blastoffnetwork.com 2012-04-02

# 

Our postal address is:  
5760 Legacy Drive  
Ste B3-534  
Plano, TX 75024

We can be reached via e-mail at info@blastoffnetwork.com Your privacy is important to Blastoff Communications, LLC., so we have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our websites and when we serve advertisements on our network of websites (collectively, the “Blastoff Network”), why we collect it and how it is used.

The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to the web surfer and/or consumer utilizing our Network. The terms “Blastoff Communications, Blastoff Network, Blastoff” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Blastoff Communications, LLC. and its partners.

Please read this privacy policy carefully since by visiting this site and sharing information with Blastoff you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our website Terms and Conditions. To the extent there is a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and a written agreement to which Blastoff is party, the terms of such agreement shall prevail with respect to the parties to that agreement.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, , disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the Website.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by or clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails sent on behal of company.

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by or selecting the option which states that you do not which to have your information shared.

Blastoff Communications is very sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Blastoff Communications’ website, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children under 13. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain PII or non-personally identifiable information on our websites from persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the Blastoff Communications’ websites at any time or in any manner. Any person who provides their information to us through the login page for new customers or website users or any other part of the Blastoff Network represents to us that they are 13 years of age or older. If we learn that PII of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on our websites without verified parental consent, then we will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

Blastoff Communicationsis committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. § 7701).

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above.

Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, financial information (e.g., credit card account information) that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them , a description of information that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by or logging in to their account and going to the Account Settings tab.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, transaction information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site.

Consumers can have this information corrected by or logging in to their account and going to the Account Settings tab and making the appropriate changes.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office.

We use third-party advertising technology vendors to collect, via includes, cookies and web beacons (1×1 pixels), non-personally identifiable data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We use third-party companies to serve advertisements on the Website. These companies may use cookies and may collect other tracking information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this Website and other websites. These companies may use the information that they collect to measure and research the effectiveness of advertisements, to track page usage and paths followed during visits, and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may provide this data to us, but only in aggregate form.
